<color=#7fa0ff><b>RimCentaurs - Story of an exotic lone wolf species
by siiftun1857</b> (AKA Magnussiiftun1857)
Licensed under Apache 2.0 (Copyright 2018)</color>

<color=#a0a0a0>None believes that centaurs exist in the world, and no one has witnessed the appearance of centaurs, or even thought about it.

Until you showed up.

You may the last centaur among you know. However, are you the only centaur in the world?

You will find out.</color>


<b><color=#ff7f00>This mod is WIP and some objects are unobtainable,
including "Thermo Damper" and "Subsystems".</color>
Requires "Explorite Core" and "Humanoid Alien Races 2.0" to work.</b>

<b>Features:</b>
- New race "Centaur" with lone wolf style scenario.
- Completely different with most races in many ways, including immune to pain shock.
- No NPC Centaur factions among the planet, you are the only one.
- Survival will not be a problem nor challenge for centaurs. Have a relax.
- Exotic resources, including archotech components.
- Unique mechanics and systems, subsystems, and pawn shield.
- Storyline of seeking "The other".
- Multiple method-patches to solve common alien races issue.
- Designed no effect on humans or other alien-races saves.
- ... and more.
<b>Integrations with Royalty:</b>
- Join the empire and satisfy royal apparel requirement without headdress.
- Release powerful abilities exclusive to centaurs.
- Psychic sensitivity of centaur will not boost Neural heat limit until it reached 300%.
- Receives no pain boost to speeds up neural heat dissipation of centaur. Just don't get hurt.
<b>Integrations with Ideology:</b>
- Centaur ideo is locked into a fixed one.
- Memes which exclusive to centaurs match their lone wolf style.
- Centaur headdress is no needs to be dyed.
<b>Integrations with SOS2:</b>
- Start in centaur cruiser.
- Uses centaur power armor as space suit, even without helmet.
- Torpedo spinal weapon.

<b>Features with SOS2:</b>
 - Start in centaur cruiser.
 - Uses centaur power armor as space suit, even without helmet.
 - Torpedo spinal weapon.

Have your nice trip!

GitHub repository: https://github.com/Exploriters/RimCentaurs
Fell free to sent pull request.
