<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Centaur Civilian -->

  <Apparel_CentaurPants.label>centaur pants</Apparel_CentaurPants.label>
  <Apparel_CentaurPants.description>A pair of pants suited for an equine body. Now we know how a horse would wear pants.</Apparel_CentaurPants.description>

  <Apparel_CentaurBasicShirt.label>centaur T-shirt</Apparel_CentaurBasicShirt.label>
  <Apparel_CentaurBasicShirt.description>A modified T-shirt for use by centaurs.</Apparel_CentaurBasicShirt.description>

  <Apparel_CentaurCollarShirt.label>button-down centaur shirt</Apparel_CentaurCollarShirt.label>
  <Apparel_CentaurCollarShirt.description>Designed for centaurs, this collared shirt comes with skirting and tiedowns to suit.</Apparel_CentaurCollarShirt.description>


  <!-- Centaur Armour -->

  <Apparel_CentaurShieldArmor.label>centaur shield vest</Apparel_CentaurShieldArmor.label>
  <Apparel_CentaurShieldArmor.description>A suit of light powered armor for a centaur wearer with projectile-repulsion device. Layered plasteel-weave plates are very effective at stopping attacks, with few vulnerable joint sections. Neuro-memetic assistors allow a centaur to wear the armor and still move easily.\n\nThe shield of it will attempt to stop incoming projectiles or shrapnel, but does nothing against melee attacks or heat. It shuts down instantly if hit by EMP. It DOES NOT prevents the wearer from firing out.\n\nArmor like this is often used by imperial janissaries and rapid-incursion space marines.\n\nAdditional weight and materials are required when compared to humanoid armor, allowing for protection of the flanks.</Apparel_CentaurShieldArmor.description>

  <Apparel_CentaurFlakVest.label>centaur flak vest</Apparel_CentaurFlakVest.label>
  <Apparel_CentaurFlakVest.description>Flak armor modified for a centaur wearer. Additional weight and materials are required when compared to humanoid vests, allowing for protection of the flanks. This armor design does not protect the limbs.</Apparel_CentaurFlakVest.description>

  <Apparel_CentaurFlakPants.label>centaur flak pants</Apparel_CentaurFlakPants.label>
  <Apparel_CentaurFlakPants.description>Modified pants suited to a centaur. The addition of armored plating grants effective protection from attacks without restricting movements.</Apparel_CentaurFlakPants.description>

  <Apparel_CentaurFlakJacket.label>centaur flak jacket</Apparel_CentaurFlakJacket.label>
  <Apparel_CentaurFlakJacket.description>An armoured overcoat suited for a centaur. A step below plate armor, the defense offered is by no means insignificant and still doesn't impede movement.</Apparel_CentaurFlakJacket.description>


</LanguageData>